<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Talend Developer Portal on API Portal</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Talend Developer Portal on API Portal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/apis/api-definitions/1.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/apis/api-definitions/1.0.0/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/apis/user-management/1.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/apis/user-management/1.0.0/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/apis/user-management/1.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/apis/user-management/1.1.0/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/docs/tutorials/deploying-api-def-to-aws-api-gateway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/docs/tutorials/deploying-api-def-to-aws-api-gateway/</guid>
      <description>Deploying an API definition to AWS API Gateway This example explains how to import a new API definition or update an existing one in AWS API Gateway from Talend Cloud API Designer.
To do this, you first have to fetch your API from Talend Cloud, then you need to deploy it to AWS API Gateway using a command line script or a CI/CD pipeline.
The following procedures use AWS CLI, but you can also use the AWS API Gateway REST API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/docs/tutorials/deploying-api-def-to-azure-api-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/docs/tutorials/deploying-api-def-to-azure-api-management/</guid>
      <description>Deployingggg an API definition to Azure API Management This example explains how to import a new API definition or update an existing one in Azure API Management from Talend Cloud API Designer.
To do this, you first have to fetch your API from Talend Cloud, then you need to deploy it to Azure API Management using a command line script or a CI/CD pipeline.
The following procedures use Microsoft PowerShell, but you can also use the Azure API Management REST API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Release Notes Latest changes available for Talend Cloud APIs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/docs/tutorials/automating-remote-engine-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/docs/tutorials/automating-remote-engine-creation/</guid>
      <description>Automating Remote Engine creation Manage engine clusters, create Remote Engines and make them ready to run by pairing them quickly.
Generating a Personal Access Token Use Personal Access Tokens to authenticate to Talend Cloud APIs or to connect Talend Studio to Talend Cloud. You generate these access tokens from Talend Cloud in the form of JSON Web Tokens (JWT).
Access Tokens are personal and the permissions they grant are synchronized with the user&amp;rsquo;s permissions, at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use cases</title>
      <link>/use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/use-cases/</guid>
      <description>Use cases Browse APIs and tutorials depending on your use cases.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
